Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward Harriman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Speeches and Writings, 1973-1992 (Box I:209-221)
  - Speeches (Box I:209)
    - Files
      - 1986
        - Apr. 22
          - Democrats for the 80's dinner, Washington, D.C.
          - Harriman Communications Center dedication, Washington, D.C.
        - Apr. 25, National Federation of Democratic Women convention, Little Rock, Ark.
        - Apr. 29, E. H. Harriman Memorial Awards luncheon, Washington, D.C.
        - May 10, Voter Registration Seminar, Democratic Party of Virginia, Williamsburg, Va.
        - May 19, fortieth anniversary of the "Iron Curtain Speech"
          - Background material for speech
          - Correspondence (Box I:217)
          - Luncheon lists
          - Publication of speech and copies sent
          - Speech
        - June 4, Democratic Business Council luncheon meeting, Washington, D.C.
        - June 22, Fairfax County Democratic Joint Campaign Committee fund-raiser, Clifton, Va.
        - June 26, Democratic Fact Book press conference, Washington, D.C.
        - Nov. 7, statement, W. Averell Harriman Award ceremony, National Democratic Institute
        - Nov. 13, Democratic National Convention Site Selection Committee tribute to W. Averell Harriman, Washington, D.C.
        - Dec. 9, tribute to Marshall Darrow Shulman, Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
        - Various introductions and unidentified speeches
      - 1987
        - Feb. 10, Jim Wright dinner, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Mar. 21, Harriman Society of Westchester dinner, Eastchester, N.Y.
        - Oct. 16, Franklin D. Roosevelt Four Freedoms Awards Ceremony, Hyde Park, N.Y.
      - 1988, Mar. 24, remarks on the Democrats for the 80's, College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Va. (Box I:218)
      - 1989
        - Feb. 21, public service speech, Groton School, Groton, Mass.
        - May 31, E. H. Harriman Memorial Awards event
        - June 12, Democrats for the 90's dinner, Washington, D.C.
        - June 22, tribute to Lloyd Bentsen, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - July 26, Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee luncheon and dinner
        - Aug. 1, Democratic Governors' Association conference, Chicago, Ill.
        - Oct. 20, Texas Democratic Women of Harris County, Houston, Tex.
      - 1990
        - Jan. 22, introduction, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Jan. 31, Democrats for the 90's evening program, Washington, D.C.
        - Mar. 28, eulogy for Girard P. Clark
        - May 16, speech on a recent trip to the Soviet Union, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Various introductions
      - 1991
        - Dec. 7, Pearl Harbor Memorial Ceremony, Hofstra University, Hempstead, N.Y.
        - Various introductions
      - 1992, speech, Denver, Colo.
      - Undated speeches
  - Writings by Harriman (Box I:219)
    - 1980, "Rebuilding the Party from the Grass Roots Up," Washington Post
    - 1982, "For 2 Healthy Parties," New York Times
    - 1983
      - "Churchill's Dream," American Heritage
      - "Reagan, Not Congress, to Blame for Deficits," Fauquier Democrat
      - Unpublished op-ed piece on British elections
    - 1984
      - "Churchill and Reagan," New York Times
      - "What Democrats Will Have to Do to Beat Reagan," Orlando Sentinel
      - "Who Says Reagan's a Shoo-in?," Washington Post
      - "Will Reagan Be Picked Off by a Modern-Day Attlee?," International Herald Tribune
    - 1986
      - Preface to the Democratic Fact Book
      - "What Churchill Really Said," Washington Post
    - 1987, "In China, Kremlin Watching," New York Times
    - 1988
      - "On Foreign Policy, the Democrats Are Back on Track," Washington Post
      - Proposed op-ed piece on Perestroika
      - "Turkey Deserves Priority Attention," New York Times See also Part I: Oversize, (3 folders)
    - 1989
      - Drafts of "Good, but Not Enough, Mr. President" (Box I:220)
      - "Have the Democrats Lost Their Soul?," New York Times
    - 1990
      - Drafts of an op-ed piece on a trip to the Soviet Union
      - "An Eyewitness Report from the U.S.S.R.," New Mexican
      - Introduction, Eleanor Roosevelt's My Day
      - "A Lesson from Truman on Aid," Boston Globe
      - Letter to the editor, Time magazine
      - "The Second Russian Revolution," Atlantic Council of the United States Special Report
    - 1991, "When Churchill Heard the News...," Washington Post
    - 1992
      - Drafts of "A Call for Democratic Party Unity"
      - "Our Moscow Blinders," Washington Post
  - Writings by others, draft of a novel by John Bowles, IV, undated, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:221)
- Part I: Scheduling and Travel, 1959-1997 (Box I:221-I:299)
  Engagement calendars, scheduling binders, invitations, miscellaneous notes and calendars, and event and trip files containing correspondence, itineraries, programs, lists, photographs, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and thereunder chronologically.
  - Engagement calendars (Box I:221)
    - 1959-1962, 1964-1965, (2 folders)
    - 1966-1974, (4 folders) (Box I:222)
    - 1975-1980, 1982-1986, 1989, (5 folders) (Box I:223)
    - 1990-1991, 1993, 1997 (Box I:224)
  - Events file
    - 1969-1972, (4 folders)
    - 1973, (2 folders) (Box I:225)
    - 1974
      - Jan.-July
      - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:226)
    - 1975
      - Feb.-June
      - Sept.-Nov. (Box I:227)
    - 1976
      - Jan.-July, (2 folders)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Box I:228)
    - 1976, Dec.-1977, Jan., presidential inauguration
    - 1977 (Box I:229)
      - Charles A. Lindbergh Memorial Fund Dinner, May, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:230)
      - General
        - Feb.-Sept.
        - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:231)
    - 1978
      - Feb.-Sept.
      - Oct.-Dec. (Box I:232)
    - 1979, Oct.-Nov.
    - 1980
      - Mar.-Aug.
      - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:233)
    - 1980-1981, dinner requests
    - 1981, Feb.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box I:234)
    - 1982 (Box I:235)
      - Jan.-Apr., (3 folders)
      - May-Aug., (3 folders) (Box I:236)
      - Sept.-Oct., (3 folders) (Box I:237)
      - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:238)
    - 1983, Jan.-July
    - 1986
      - Apr.-Nov.
      - Dec. (Box I:239)
    - 1987
      - Feb.-May
      - June-Dec., (3 folders) (Box I:240)
    - 1988
      - Jan.-May, (3 folders) (Box I:241)
      - June-Sept., (3 folders) (Box I:242)
      - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box I:243)
    - 1989
      - Feb.-May, (4 folders) (Box I:244)
      - May-Sept., (4 folders) (Box I:245)
      - Sept.-Oct., (3 folders) (Box I:246)
      - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:247)
    - 1990
      - Jan.-Feb.
      - Mar.-Apr., (3 folders) (Box I:248)
      - Apr.-May, (4 folders) (Box I:249)
      - May-June, (3 folders) (Box I:250)
      - June-Sept., (4 folders) (Box I:251)
      - Oct., (2 folders) (Box I:252)
      - Oct.-Nov., (3 folders) (Box I:253)
      - Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:254)
    - 1991
      - Jan.
      - Feb.-Apr., (4 folders) (Box I:255)
      - Apr.-May, (3 folders) (Box I:256)
      - May-July, (4 folders) (Box I:257)
      - Sept.-Nov., (3 folders) (Box I:258)
      - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:259)
    - 1992
      - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
      - Mar.-June, (4 folders) (Box I:260)
      - July-Oct., (3 folders) (Box I:261)
      - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box I:262)
    - 1993 (Box I:263)
      - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
      - Mar.-May, (3 folders) (Box I:264)
  - Invitations (Box I:265)
    - 1988
      - Jan.-May, (7 folders)
      - May-July, (6 folders) (Box I:266)
      - Aug.-Oct., (7 folders) (Box I:267)
      - Oct., (2 folders) (Box I:268)
    - 1989-1993, undated
  - Miscellaneous records and calendars
    - 1972-1982, (3 folders)
    - 1983, (3 folders) (Box I:269)
    - 1984, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:270, Box I:271)
    - 1985, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:272)
    - 1986, (2 folders) (Box I:273)
    - 1987, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:274)
    - 1988-1989, (2 folders)
    - 1990, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:275, Box I:276)
    - 1991
    - 1992-1993, undated, (3 folders) (Box I:277)
  - Scheduling binders (Box I:278)
    - 1988-1989, (2 folders)
    - 1990-1991, (3 folders) (Box I:279)
    - 1992, (2 folders) (Box I:280)
  - Social events away, 1976-1978, (2 folders)
  - Trips (Box I:281)
    - Lists of travel, 1995, undated
    - circa 1965, Republic of the Congo
    - 1967, China See also Part I: Oversize
    - 1972, France and Great Britain
    - 1973, France and Great Britain
    - 1974
      - Great Britain
      - Soviet Union See also Oversize, (5 folders)
    - 1975
      - Great Britain
      - Soviet Union, (2 folders)
    - 1976, Great Britain, Soviet Union, and Yugoslavia (Box I:282)
    - 1978
      - Australia
      - Belgium, France, Great Britain, and Soviet Union
      - Great Britain
      - Hungary, Romania, and Yugoslavia, (4 folders)
      - Panama (Box I:283)
    - 1979
      - Mexico
      - Yugoslavia
    - 1980
      - Yugoslavia
      - Zimbabwe, (4 folders)
    - 1981, Barbados
    - 1983
      - Great Britain
      - Soviet Union, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box I:284, Box I:285, Box I:286, Box I:287, Box I:288)
    - 1984, Great Britain
    - 1985
      - France
      - Great Britain
    - 1986
      - Great Britain, May
      - Great Britain, Dec.
    - 1987
      - China and Hong Kong, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box I:289, Box I:290)
      - Egypt, Israel, and Jordan, (4 folders)
      - France and Great Britain (Box I:291)
      - France and Turkey, (3 folders)
      - Japan, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:292)
      - Soviet Union
    - 1988
      - France
      - Great Britain and Italy
    - 1989
      - Belgium, France, Germany and Great Britain, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:293)
      - France
      - Turkey, (2 folders)
    - 1990
      - France and Great Britain
      - Great Britain
      - Kuwait, Oman, and Saudi Arabia, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box I:294, Box I:295)
      - Soviet Union, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:296, Box I:297)
    - 1991
      - China
      - France
    - 1992
      - France and Great Britain
      - Great Britain (Box I:298)
      - Portugal and Spain
      - Russia, Ukraine, and Uzbekistan, (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:299)
    - 1993
      - India and Pakistan
      - Morocco, (3 folders)
- Part I: Miscellany, 1909-1997 (Box I:229-I:328)
  Address books and Rolodexes; biographical statements; interview transcripts and correspondence related to proposed biographies; card files; diary excerpts, memoranda of conversations, and trip reports; files from Harriman's personal desk; guest books from her various residences; press clippings, interview requests and transcripts; scrapbooks; and telephone call sheets.
  - Addresses (Box I:229)
    - Address books (most dating is approximate)
      - Late 1940s, Paris, France
      - 1950s (Box I:300)
      - 1960-1961
      - 1963
      - 1968 (Box I:301)
      - 1970s-1980s
      - 1980s, Barbados
      - 1991
      - Undated
    - Binders
      - 1988
      - Undated, (1 folder) (Box I:302)
    - Card files
      - 1972-1982, N-Z See Part I: Oversize
      - 1981-1982, foreign addresses See Part I: Oversize
      - Undated
    - Engagement calendar address pages See Container I:221, Engagement calendars
    - Rolodexes
      - Cards, 1970s-1990s See Oversize
      - Computer printouts, 1984, (2 folders)
    - Updated information, circa 1980s-1990s, (1 folder) (Box I:303)
  - Biographical statements
    - Harriman, Pamela, 1982-1991
    - Harriman, W. Averell, 1986
  - Biographies and proposed biographies
    - Background
      - Chronologies, circa 1991
      - Correspondence, 1991
      - Miscellaneous notes, circa 1991
      - Newspaper clippings, 1937-1946, 1964, (3 folders)
      - Published primary and secondary sources
        - Notes, circa 1991
        - Photocopies, 1947-1981, undated
      - Reminiscences and notes by Harriman, 1990-1991
      - Topics (Box I:304)
        - Harriman, W. Averell, 1915, 1941-1991
        - Murrow, Edward R., 1949-1991
    - Billington, Joy, 1982-1983
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1991
    - Ogden, Chris
      - Book expenses, 1991
      - Correspondence and proposal, 1991-1993
      - Interview transcripts, 1991
        - July-Oct. 1, (3 folders)
        - Oct. 1-Nov., (8 folders) (Box I:305)
      - Legal file, 1991-1993
      - Random House, 1991 (Box I:306)
    - Smith, Sally Bedell, 1991-1993
  - Birthday celebrations, 1984, undated, (6 folders)
  - Card file with guest lists, important dates, supplier lists, and loose business cards, 1971-1980 See Part I: Oversize
  - Cash reports, 1991-1992, (3 folders)
  - Christmas, 1985, 1992 (Box I:307)
  - Death of Pamela Harriman
    - Eulogy by Bill Clinton, 1997
    - Funeral wishes, 1983
  - Diary excerpts, memoranda of conversations, and trip reports, 1973-1976, 1983, 1986-1993, undated, (7 folders)
  - Files from her desk at 3032 "N" Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
    - American-Russian Cultural Cooperation Foundation, 1992
    - Casablanca Conference Revisited, Casablanca, Morocco, 1993, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:308)
    - Churchill College, Cambridge, England, 1986
    - Clifford, Clark M., 1989, undated
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1992
    - Cuomo, Mario M., 1984-1986
    - Doolittle, James, Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1989
    - Foley, Thomas S., 1988-1989
    - Forest Lake, N.Y., 1986, undated
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich and Raisa Maksimovna, visit, 1987
    - Harriman, W. Averell, funeral and eulogies, 1986
    - Hopkins, Harry L., 1985-1986
    - Mandela, Nelson, luncheon, 1993
    - Mideast trip, State Department briefing, 1993
    - Morocco, 1993
    - Personal, 1909, 1963, 1976, 1986-1988
    - Photographs, 1990-1992, undated, (3 folders)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr., 1989 (Box I:309)
    - Shulman, Marshall Darrow, 1988-1990
    - Single European market, 1992
  - Files from her desk at 3032 "N" Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
    - Soviet Union
      - Andropov, Yuri, 1983-1985
      - Arbatov, Georgy, 1986-1992
      - Black Sea, 1975-1992
      - Burlatsky, Feador M., 1988-1989
      - Central Committee theses for the All-Union Party conference, 1988
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich
        - Reforms, 1988
        - Speech at the United Nations, 1988
      - Harriman, W. Averell, Soviet statements, 1962-1963
      - Other materials, 1986-1992
      - Sakharov, Andrei, 1988
    - Swiers, Peter, 1988
    - Valéry, François, 1987
    - Wickersham, George W., Cathedral Church of Saint John the Divine, New York, N.Y., undated
  - Frequently called telephone numbers, 1990, undated
  - Guest books (Box I:310)
    - 3038 "N" Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
      - 1972-1983, (4 folders)
      - 1983-1985, 1990, (5 folders) (Box I:311)
      - 1986-1993 See also Oversize, (4 folders) (Box I:312)
    - Birchgrove ("Haywire House"), Yorktown Heights, N.Y., 1962-1986 (Box I:313)
    - Hobe Sound, Fla., 1971-1978
    - Mango Bay, Barbados, 1984-1993
    - Willow Oaks estate, Middleburg, Va., 1978-1979
  - Press
    - Clippings (Box I:314)
      - 1937-1946, 1958-1982 See also Part I: Oversize, (17 folders)
      - 1983-1987, (6 folders) (Box I:315)
      - 1988, (1 folder) (Box I:316)
      - 1989-1996 See also Oversize, (10 folders)
      - 1997, undated, (2 folders) (Box I:317)
    - Correspondence, including interview requests
      - 1971-1992, (7 folders)
      - 1993, undated (Box I:318)
    - Features
      - Architectural Digest, 1983-1984, (2 folders)
      - New Republic, 1988, (3 folders)
      - Savvy magazine, 1987-1988
      - Vanity Fair, 1988
    - Interview transcripts, 1978-1992, (2 folders)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1980 (Box I:319)
      - National Mental Health Association's salute to Rosalyn Carter
      - Union Pacific and Western Pacific Inspection Special See Oversize
    - 1981, W. Averell Harriman's ninetieth birthday celebration See Oversize
    - 1982
      - Largely thank-you letters from political figures
      - Overview of the year's events
    - 1983, Win the Senate '84 campaign See Oversize
    - 1984
      - Democratic National Convention, San Francisco, Calif. See Oversize
      - Letters from political figures and prominent Washingtonians See Oversize
    - 1985, largely letters from political figures See Oversize
    - 1986, largely letters from political figures
  - Speech training, 1985, undated
  - Stationery, undated
  - Telephone call sheets
    - Filed copies
      - 1980
      - 1985
        - Jan.-Oct., (3 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box I:320)
      - 1986
        - Jan.-June, (4 folders)
        - July-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:321)
      - 1987
        - Harriman, Pamela, (3 folders)
        - Howard, Janet A., (2 folders)
      - 1988
        - Harriman, Pamela
          - Jan.-Aug., (2 folders)
          - Sept.-Dec. (Box I:322)
        - Howard, Janet A., (5 folders)
      - 1989 (Box I:323)
        - Harriman, Pamela, (2 folders)
        - Howard, Janet A.
          - Jan.-Aug., (4 folders)
          - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:324)
      - 1990
        - Harriman, Pamela, (4 folders)
        - Howard, Janet A. (Box I:325)
          - Set 1
          - Set 2, (5 folders)
      - 1991
        - Harriman, Pamela
          - Jan.-Mar.
          - Apr.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box I:326)
        - Howard, Janet A.
      - 1992
        - Harriman, Pamela, (3 folders)
        - Howard, Janet A.
      - 1993
        - Harriman, Pamela
          - Jan.-Mar.
          - Apr.-May (Box I:327)
        - Howard, Janet A.
    - Unsorted sheets and call lists, circa 1983-1993, (2 folders) (Box I:328)
- Part I: Artifact, 1967 (Box I:VA 1)
  Gold medal depicting Konrad Adenauer and designed by Salvador Dali.
  - Adenauer, Konrad, gold medal designed by Salvador Dali, 1967 (Box I:VA 1)
- Part I: Classified, 1944-1996 (Box I:CL 1)
  Correspondence, cables, memoranda, an operational order, and talking points.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Part I: Personal and Family Papers (Box I:CL 1)
    - Family Papers
      - Churchill family
        - Churchill, Winston S. (son) and Minnie d"Erlanger (daughter-in-law)
          - Miscellany, undated (Container I:7)
    - Personal Papers
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1944 (Container I:27)
  - Part I: General Correspondence
    - Alphabetical File
      - Kipper, Judith, 1989-1991 (Container I:106)
  - Part I: Ambassadorial File
    - Alphabetical correspondence file
      - 1993, "B" (Container I:181)
      - 1996, "D" (Container I:188)
- Part I: Oversize, 1947-1997 (Box I:OV 1-I:OV 28)
  Oversize items consisting of Rolodex and other card files, photograph albums, scrapbooks, awards and certificates, correspondence, news clippings, and other printed matter.
  - Part I: Personal and Family Papers (Box I:OV 1)
    - Family Papers
      - Churchill family
        - Churchill, Winston S. (son) and Minnie d'Erlanger (daughter-in-law)
          - Correspondence, 1963 (Container I:3)
      - Harriman family (Box I:OV 2)
        - Harriman, Marie Norton Whitney, card file for entertaining, 1962-1965 (Container I:10)
        - Harriman, W. Averell (husband) (Box I:OV 3)
          - Death and funeral, 1986
            - Condolences
              - Incoming, "C" (Container I:13)
            - News clippings
              - Scrapbook (Container I:19)
            - Services
              - Funeral, New York, N.Y.
                - Guest book (Container I:20)
              - Memorial, Washington, D.C.
                - Guest book (Container I:20)
              - Miscellany, 1947, 1952, 1967, 1973, and undated (Container I:21) (Box I:OV 4)
        - Mortimer, David H. and Shelley Wanger, 1986 (Container I:23)
    - Personal Papers
      - Correspondence
        - Clinton, Bill, 1996 (Container I:26)
  - Part I: General Correspondence
    - Brown, Ronald Harmon, 1989 (Container I:53)
    - Coehlo, Tony, 1982 (Container I:64)
    - District of Columbia
      - Democratic State Committee, undated (Container I:78)
      - Presidential inauguration "no parking" signs, 1961, 1973, 1977, 1985 (Container I:78)
  - Part I: Ambassadorial File (Box I:OV 5)
    - Scheduling
      - Card file, 1993-1997 (Container I:203)
  - Part I: Speeches and Writings (Box I:OV 6)
    - Writings
      - 1988
        - "Turkey Deserves Priority Attention," New York Times (Container I:219)
  - Part I: Scheduling and Travel (Box I:OV 7)
    - Trips
      - 1967
        - China (Container I:281)
      - 1974 (Box I:OV 8)
        - Soviet Union (Container I:281)
  - Part I: Miscellany (Box I:OV 9)
    - Addresses
      - Card files (Container I:302)
        - 1972-1982, N-Z
        - 1981-1982, foreign addresses
      - Rolodexes (Container I:302) (Box I:OV 10)
        - Cards, 1970s-1990s
          - Rolodex #1, A-Z
          - Rolodex #2 (Box I:OV 11)
            - A-R
            - S-Z (Box I:OV 12)
          - Rolodex #3, A-Z
          - Rolodex #4 (Box I:OV 13)
            - A-L
            - M-Z (Box I:OV 14)
          - Rolodex # 5, A-Z (Box I:OV 15)
          - Rolodex #6 (Box I:OV 16)
            - A-L
            - M-Z (Box I:OV 17)
          - Rolodex #7, A-N (incomplete)
          - Rolodex #8 (Box I:OV 18)
            - A-Q
            - R-Z (Box I:OV 19)
          - Rolodex #9, A-Z
          - Rolodex #10, A-Z (Box I:OV 20)
          - Rolodex #11, A-Z
          - Rolodex #12, A-Z (Box I:OV 21)
    - Card file with guest lists, important dates, supplier lists, and loose business cards, 1971-1980 (Container I:306) (Box I:OV 22)
    - Guest books (Box I:OV 23)
      - 3038 "N" Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
        - 1986-1993 (Container I:312)
    - Press (Box I:OV 24)
      - Clippings
        - 1982 (Container I:314)
        - 1992 (Container I:316) (Box I:OV 25)
    - Scrapbooks (Box I:OV 26)
      - 1980
        - Union Pacific and Western Pacific Inspection Special (Container I:319)
      - 1981, W. Averell Harriman's ninetieth birthday celebration (Container I:319) (Box I:OV 27)
      - 1983, Win the Senate '84 campaign (Container I:319)
      - 1984 (Box I:OV 28)
        - Democratic National Convention, San Francisco, Calif. (Container I:319)
        - Letters from political figures and prominent Washingtonians (Container I:319)
      - 1985, largely letters from political figures (Container I:319)
- Part II: Subject File, 1968-1993 (Box II:1-II:79)
  Correspondence, agenda, minutes, reports, briefing binders, proposals, polls, event programs, brochures and other campaign literature, newsletters, lists, speeches and writings by others, news clippings, and other printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person or organization, topic, or type of material.
  - Abortion rights, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box II:1)
  - Absentee voting, 1989, (2 folders)
  - Addy Awards, 1987
  - America Votes, 1987
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1989, undated
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1986
  - American Political Network, Hotline newsletter
    - 1987-1991
    - 1992, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:2)
  - American Political Report, 1982-1992
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1981-1992, (2 folders)
  - Analysis Group, 1981-1990, (4 folders) (Box II:3)
  - Annenberg Washington Program, Northwestern University, Evanston, Ill., 1988
  - Appleseed Enterprises, 1993
  - Association of State Democratic Chairs, 1988-1991
  - Association of State Democratic Executive Directors, 1982-1985
  - Barber, Frank, 1987
  - Baron Report, 1980-1985
  - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1989
  - Biden, Joseph R., 1983-1987 (Box II:4)
  - Billings, Leon G., reports, 1983-1989
  - Bird, Rose, 1985
  - Blanchard, James J., 1988-1990